cambridgelms.org 2017-10-28

# Privacy Policy: Cambridge LMS

#### Cambridge Learning Management System -  
Data Protection & Privacy Policy ('Policy')

  1. ##### 1\. About us

    1. This website is owned and operated by The Chancellor Masters and Scholars of the University of Cambridge acting through its departments, Cambridge University Press (‘Cambridge University Press’) and Cambridge English Language Assessment (‘Cambridge Assessment’). Cambridge University Press and Cambridge Assessment are our operating names (referred to collectively in this policy as ‘Cambridge’ or ‘we’).

  2. ##### 2\. Our approach

    1. 2.1 Cambridge is committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of information provided by those parties (‘users’/‘you’) who access the Cambridge Learning Management System website (‘the website’)

    2. 2.2 User privacy is important to Cambridge. We want to make sure that when we collect information from users we do so in a way that does not infringe your privacy. This policy explains how we do this.

    3. 2.3 We uphold the relevant data protection principles and process all personal data in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

    4. 2.4 By registering or purchasing anything on this website, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this policy.

    5. 2.5 This policy forms part of the website terms of use http://www.cambridgelms.org/main/p/termsofuse

  3. ##### 3\. Collection of personal information

    1. 3.1 When you register to use the website, or use or purchase some of the online services via the website we may need to collect and process various personal data from you, namely: names, email and postal addresses, telephone numbers, professions, purchase and mailing history.

    2. 3.2 You agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by the relevant registration form.

    3. 3.3 Where you register for an account on the website you agree to maintain and promptly update your user profile information to keep it true, accurate, current and complete.

    4. 3.4 Please note that should you choose to post material on the website forums, and include personal data such as your name on these forums, this is not deemed to be collection by Cambridge of your personal data.

    5. 3.5 Where you post user content, you must not include the personal data of other individuals unless you obtain their prior consent.

  4. ##### 4\. Processing of personal information

    1. 4.1 The information you provide will enable us to provide you with access to our website and to carry out administrative functions such as populating your user profile with your name.

    2. 4.2 If you have requested any goods or services then we will use your information to supply the goods or services, to bill you and to contact you where necessary concerning your purchase.

    3. 4.3 Cambridge may use statistical data arising out of use of the website by users for internal editorial purposes, academic research purposes and to monitor usage of the website and particular content on the website, in accordance with the Terms of Use. No personal data will be included in this statistical data.

    4. 4.4 We are committed to maintaining high standards for the website and we may use any information you provide as part of your use or registration to the website to guide us in assessing and improving the website.

    5. 4.5 The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.

    6. 4.6 By providing your own personal data you consent to our processing that data as described above.

  5. ##### 5\. Modifying/removing your personal information

    1. 5.1 You may correct or update your registered details on your user profile page. You can do this by clicking on your name under the heading 'My Account'. Where your user profile does not allow you to correct or update your details, or where you wish your personal data to be removed from our systems contact us via lms.support@cambridge.org.

    2. 5.2 You are entitled to see the information held about you. If you wish to see the information held about you, please contact us by emailing or writing to Legal Services at the address detailed in section 7 below. We are entitled by law to charge a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

  6. ##### 6\. Disclosure of Information to third parties

    1. 6.1. Where you have consented, Cambridge may contact you on occasion by email about products and services we think might be of interest to you. If you decide in the future that you do not want to receive such information, please email mlist@cambridge.org.

    2. 6.2 Cambridge may transfer your personal details to other regions in which we have offices throughout the world, namely Europe, the Middle East and Africa; the Americas; India and Asia-Pacific. You should be aware that some of our offices are in countries which do not have data protection laws. If you do not want us to make the information available in this way email mlist@cambridge.org..

    3. 6.3 We may disclose your information to our agents and service providers for the purposes set out above.

    4. 6.4 Except as detailed above, we will use our reasonable endeavours not to disclose the data we have received to any third parties, unless we are required to do so by law or any court order or you have provided consent to such disclosure.

  7. ##### 7\. Cookies

    1. 7.1 Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.

    2. 7.2 A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive.

    3. 7.3 The cookies we use are "analytical" cookies. They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around the site when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.

    4. 7.4 Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.

    5. 7.5 You block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our site.

  8. ##### 8\. Comments/questions

    1. In the event of any comments or questions concerning this policy, please contact us by e-mailing Legal Services at legalservices@cambridge.org or writing to The Legal Services Director, Cambridge University Press, University Printing House, Shaftesbury Road, Cambridge, CB2 8BS, England

  9. ##### 9\. Changes to this policy

    1.  **Any changes to this policy in the future will be posted to the website and, where appropriate, given to you through email notification.**

  10.  **Last Updated:** 2 September 2014
